A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Returns to Auditor on Manufacture of Salt, Lead, Iron, and Segars, 1815
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Returns to Auditor on Manufacture of Salt, Lead, Iron, and Segars, 1815
The Library of Virginia
APA 387
.25 cu. ft. (1 box)
Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Auditor of Public Accounts in 1913.
Biographical Information
The General Assembly passed an act on 11 January 1815 levying taxes on salt, lead, iron, and segars (cigars) manufactured in Virginia. The act required that manufacturers of those products obtain licenses from local courts and that local officials make regular reports to the auditor of public accounts on the amounts of goods manufactured and sold. The act was repealed on 27 February 1816.
Scope and Content
Returns to Auditor, 1815, reporting on the amounts of salt, lead, iron, and segars (cigars) manufactured and sold in Virginia counties. The returns list the names of manufacturers and the amounts produced. Includes correspondence, receipts, and returns.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- Accomack County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Augusta County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Botetourt County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Brooke County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cabell County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Campbell County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Chesterfield County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Elizabeth City County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Essex County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Franklin County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Grayson County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Greenbrier County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Harrison County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Henrico County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Kanawha County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Monongalia County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Northampton County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Northumberland County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Patrick County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Princess Anne County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Rockbridge County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Rockingham County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Shenandoah County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Tyler County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Warwick County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Washington County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Wythe County, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Wrappers, 1815 (Box 1, Folder 28)